<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rami Sabbagh on Rami's Blog</title><link>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/authors/rami-sabbagh/</link><description>Recent content in Rami Sabbagh on Rami's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/authors/rami-sabbagh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hacking my router settings</title><link>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2019-08-08-hacking-my-router-settings/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2019-08-08-hacking-my-router-settings/</guid><description>Hello everyone, it&amp;rsquo;s been 2 years since the last blog post, yea, I&amp;rsquo;m such a lazy blogger 😛
Many changes have been made to my home&amp;rsquo;s network recently, my dad took full control of it&amp;hellip;
We have 2 TP-Link routers at home:
The main one, which connects with ADSL, is named InGodWeTrust_HA, The slave one, which is connected with the main one via an ethernet cable, is named InGodWeTrust_Boost. What my dad has made was:</description></item><item><title>LIKO-12 Doodle #1 - PowderV1.2</title><link>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2017-10-26-liko-12-doodle-1-powder/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2017-10-26-liko-12-doodle-1-powder/</guid><description>A powder sandbox in LIKO-12
Creating a powder sandbox in LIKO-12, is not hard at all, it only took me 2 hours to write the whole doodle.
First, I had to find a way to store the powder canvas, and for this I used an imagedata, but you may be asking, what an imagedata is ?
The LIKO-12 GPU offers 2 amazing features called images and imagedatas:
Images: They are like sprites (Sprites are actually images internaly), that you can directly draw to the screen, but without being able to edit them.</description></item><item><title>Physicsgun Update</title><link>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2015-09-29-physicsgun-update/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2015-09-29-physicsgun-update/</guid><description>Hey everyone, I have released a new version of PixelizerBox with a Physicsgun !
Download now at itch.io : http://ramilego4game.itch.io/pixelizerbox-dev-pre</description></item><item><title>Eid Mubarak</title><link>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2015-09-24-eid-mubarak/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2015-09-24-eid-mubarak/</guid><description>Eid Mubarak For ALL :)</description></item><item><title>What's going on!</title><link>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2015-07-13-whats-going-on/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2015-07-13-whats-going-on/</guid><description>It has been a long time ago since the last post, That’s because I’m being so busy programming the level editor.
I have uploaded various development videos to Youtube to see what I have done, And then created a playlist for them, There are 3 new videos and an old one motioned in the old post.
That was a lot of hard work to make it with clean, simple GUI !
Things have been done: Clean, simple GUI Code drawn grid Quick object select bar New,Save and Load buttons Infinite maps Zoom In/Out with mouse scroll Snap-To-Grid object creation Static Rectangle Soft ball to play with Object options for customization of their properties Custom error screen with bug reports Level System API Things to be done for the demo: Ability to delete objects Level spawn Connected levels system Rectangles color option Player customization Test mode Main menu Add music/sounds to the game</description></item><item><title>Skipping the prototype stage!</title><link>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2015-06-18-skipping-the-prototype-stage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2015-06-18-skipping-the-prototype-stage/</guid><description>Hello everyone, I haven’t been active for some time, But now i’m back :)
After some upgrades and rewriting some files, The engine of the game is now able to jump over the prototype stage, Because of that I’m afraid, I have to pass on it :(
Before I decided to pass on prototype stage, I had some work done on the sandbox (not and won’t be complete) which you can see here :
Now I started working on the level editor, Screenshots and videos are coming soon !</description></item><item><title>PixelizerBox V0.1.3.0 Update (Modding Support)</title><link>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2015-05-20-pixelizerbox-v0-1-3-0-update-modding-support/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2015-05-20-pixelizerbox-v0-1-3-0-update-modding-support/</guid><description>Hi Everyone, Today I pushed the first update after a long time :D
You can download it directly from itch.io page.
Now it have a side-menu for choosing object.
And you can now create mods without having to code :) !
You can find a tutorial at “/PixelizerBox/Modding Documentation.txt” and there is an example mod at “/PixelizerBox/Mods/Simple/”.
And you can download the used PhysicsEditor from Here.</description></item><item><title>Welcome Back Everyone!</title><link>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2015-05-16-welcome-back-everyone/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2015-05-16-welcome-back-everyone/</guid><description>Hey everyone :) , I’m back, Sorry for being too late :(, But i have some good news !
I started working on CJForge, It’s an engine upgrade to concerned joe that brings advanced modding to it, The main reason to start it is that Xelu is no longer updating concerned joe, For now i’m only documenting all the files in CJ files, If you want to see what i have done visit http://github.com/ramilego4game/cjforge/.
Sorry for not posting updates to Pixelizerbox, But now I have some changes to show :</description></item><item><title>Hibernating All Computers</title><link>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2015-04-21-hibernating-all-computers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2015-04-21-hibernating-all-computers/</guid><description>Hello everyone !
Today I have some good &amp;amp; bad news :)
Bad News: I’m hibernating all my computers until the end of my school tests, They start at 5/5/2015 and end at 15/5/2015 😛
Good News: After the test I can work all the week, so PixelizerBox will have alot of updates + It may exit the Prototype Stage !
Also I’ll have alot of projects :)</description></item><item><title>Hello world!</title><link>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2014-11-06-hello-world/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://rami-sabbagh.github.io/posts/2014-11-06-hello-world/</guid><description>Welcome to RamiLego4Game Website. This is my first post, So Hello everyone :)</description></item></channel></rss>